

CONTACT ME

vebarina@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/veronicabarina

github.com/vebarina

+372 5603 8208

ADDRESS

Tallinn, Estonia

SKILLS

HTML5

JavaScript ES6 (Vue.js, Vuex, React.js, React Native)

CSS3 (grid, flexbox, bootstrap, preprocessors - LESS, SASS/SCSS)

Unit, integration and component testing (Jest, React Testing Library, Vue Test Utils, Cypress)

VERONICA BARINA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated, proactive, and goal-oriented software developer with a drive for continuous learning and self-improvement.

I am experienced in working in small to medium Agile teams with a focus on Scrum methodologies, as well as independently, working on freelance projects.

I have great communication skills and attention to detail, and I excel in collaborative team environments as well as when working autonomously.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Codatina | Remote | October 2023 - Present

• I help digital agencies who need extra development resources in their projects, using technologies such as React.js, React Native, Vue.js, among others.

Software Developer

Konfuzio | Remote | April 2022 - October 2023

 As a part of the Frontend team, I am responsible for implementing new features using Vue.js, Vuex, Buefy, Git (and GitHub/GitLab), Vue Test Utils, and Cypress, delivering a high-quality product, as well as improving existing features and codebase, fixing bugs, supporting clients, and updating our documentation. My work can be found in the following open-source repository.

LANGUAGES

Spanish → Native speaker

English → Bilingual

French — Conversational

Estonian —— Beginner

Freelance React Native Developer

Pipet App | Remote | Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

• I was responsible for helping develop the frontend of a pet mobile app with React Native.

Freelance React Developer

Bien Consulting | Remote | May 2021 - Nov 2021

• I was responsible for creating the React.js frontend for a cross-platform sleep tracking app project.

EDUCATION

Mastering React

Code With Mosh | Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

Beginner JavaScript

Wes Bos | Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

CSS Grid

Wes Bos | Jun 2021

Java from Scratch

Software Development Academy (SDA) | Nov 2020 - Jul 2021

Introduction to CSS3

University of Michigan - Coursera | May 2020

Introduction to HTML5

University of Michigan - Coursera | Apr 2020 - May 2020